http://www.commercialbank-stl.com/legal-disclaimer

X
Online Banking
Username:
Enroll Now
Forgotten Username
Forgotten Password
Privacy Policy|Security Statement
Select Other Account...
News & Information
NO WARRANTIES COMMERCIAL BANK MAKES NO REPRESENTATION ABOUT THE SUITABILITY OF THE CONTENT OF THIS SITE FOR ANY PURPOSE. ALL CONTENT IS PROVIDED “AS IS” WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED. COMMERCIAL BANK DISCLAIMS ANY WARRANTIES AND REPRESENTATIONS WITH REGARD TO THE CONTENT, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, ANY IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT AND SECURITY. COMMERCIAL BANK DOES NOT WARRANT THAT THE CONTENT HEREIN IS ACCURATE, COMPLETE, OR CURRENT. COMMERCIAL BANK MAKES NO COMMITMENT TO UPDATE THE CONTENT OF THIS SITE. IT IS YOUR RESPONSIBILITY TO VERIFY ANY INFORMATION BEFORE RELYING ON IT. THE CONTENT OF THIS SITE MAY INCLUDE TECHNICAL INACCURACIES OR TYPOGRAPHICAL ERRORS. FROM TIME TO TIME CHANGES ARE MADE TO THE CONTENT DISPLAYED ON THIS SITE. COMMERCIAL BANK MAY MAKE CHANGES IN THE PRODUCTS AND/OR THE SERVICES DESCRIBED ON THIS SITE AT ANY TIME.
LIMITATION OF LIABILITY COMMERCIAL BANK WILL NOT BE LIABLE UNDER ANY CIRCUMSTANCES FOR ANY DAMAGES OR INJURY ARISING FROM YOUR USE OF THIS SITE. THIS LIMITATION ON LIABILITY INCLUDES, BUT IS NOT LIMITED TO, THE TRANSMISSION OF ANY VIRUSES WHICH MAY INFECT YOUR EQUIPMENT, FAILURE OF MECHANICAL OR ELECTRONIC EQUIPMENT OR COMMUNICATION LINES, TELEPHONE OR OTHER INTERCONNECT PROBLEMS (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, ACCESSING YOUR Internet SERVICE PROVIDER), UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS, THEFT, OPERATOR ERRORS, STRIKES OR OTHER LABOR PROBLEMS OR ANY FORCE MAJEURE. IN NO EVENT SHALL COMMERCIAL BANK BE LIABLE FOR ANY SPECIAL, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS, ARISING OUT OF OR RELATING TO THE USE OF THIS SITE OR THE COPYING OR DISPLAY OF INFORMATION ACCESSED THROUGH THIS SITE, WHETHER OR NOT COMMERCIAL BANK WAS ADVISED OF OR AWARE OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. THIS DISCLAIMER OF LIABILITY IS EFFECTIVE WITHOUT REGARD TO THE FORM OF ANY ACTON, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO CONTRACT, NEGLIGENCE, TORT, STRICT LIABILITY OR ANY OTHER THEORY. WITHOUT LIMITING THE FOREGOING, COMMERCIAL BANK SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY LOSSES OR DAMAGES INCURRED AS A RESULT OF ANY INFORMATION SUBMITTED TO IT THROUGH THIS SITE OR ANY PAGE HEREOF OR FOR ITS TRANSMISSION OF INFORMATION TO ANY PERSON(S) OR ENTITY(IES) AS A RESULT OF A REQUEST FOR SUCH TRANSMISSION REASONABLY BELIEVED BY COMMERCIAL BANK TO HAVE BEEN MADE BY SUCH PERSON OR ENTITY.
LINKS TO THIRD PARTY SITES This Site may contain links to Internet sites controlled or offered by third parties who are not affiliated with Commercial Bank. Your use of the hyperlinks on this Site to other Internet sites is at your own risk and Commercial Bank is not responsible for the accuracy or reliability of any information, data, opinions, advice or statements made on such linked sites. Commercial Bank makes no representations whatsoever concerning the content of those sites. Commercial Bank hereby disclaims liability for any information, materials, products or services posted or offered at any of the third party sites linked to this web site. A link to a site is NOT an endorsement, authorization, sponsorship, or affiliation by or with Commercial Bank with respect to such site, its owners, or its providers; these links are provided only as a convenience to you. Commercial Bank has not tested any information, software, products or services found on these sites and therefore cannot make any representations whatsoever with respect thereto. There are risks in using any information, software, products or services found on the Internet; and you should be sure that you completely understand these risks before retrieving, using, relying upon, or purchasing anything via the Internet. You should be aware that linked sites may contain rules and regulations, privacy provisions, confidentiality provisions, transmission of personal data provisions, and other provisions that differ from the provisions provided on this Site. Commercial Bank is not responsible for such provisions, and expressly disclaims any and all liability related to such provisions. The Commercial Bank’s Internet bill payment system (the “Bill Payment System”) is provided to you by (i) a linked web site owned and operated by S1 Community eFinance Solutions Group (“S1”) and (ii) bill payment processing system owned and operated by Checkfree Services Corporation (“Checkfree”). Commercial Bank has contracted with S1 and Checkfree to provide the Bill Payment System to you. S1 and Checkfree are not affiliated with or controlled by Commercial Bank.
JURISDICTION These Terms and Conditions will be governed by and be interpreted pursuant to the laws of the State of Missouri or the United States, notwithstanding any principles of conflicts of law. The state or federal courts located in St. Louis, Missouri, shall have exclusive jurisdiction over any cause of action arising out of or related to the content or use of this Site.
ENTIRE AGREEMENT If any part of these Terms and Conditions is unlawful, void, or unenforceable, that part will be deemed severable and will not affect the validity and enforceability of any remaining provisions. Commercial Bank reserves the right to seek all remedies available at law and in equity for violations of these Terms and Conditions, including the right to block access from a particular Internet address to the Site.
PRIVACY INFORMATION At Commercial Bank, maintaining the privacy of the nonpublic personal information of our consumer customers is our top priority. Commercial Bank’s Consumer Privacy Policy may be viewed at [http://www.CommercialBank-stl.com/privacyPolicy.htm]. These Terms and Conditions supplement those of the Consumer Privacy Policy. You should be aware that linked sites may contain confidentiality provisions that differ from the provisions provided herein. Commercial Bank is not responsible for such provisions, and expressly disclaims any and all liability related to such provisions. Commercial Bank uses encryption technology to protect the privacy of personal information supplied to us or accessed through our Web banking service. To provide you with better service, Commercial Bank may also use “cookies”. A cookie is a small bit of information given to your browser by a web site, which can later be retrieved. A cookie is a way for a web site to recognize whether or not you have visited the site before. The cookie cannot be read by a web site other than the one that “set” the cookie. Commercial Bank may use cookies for administrative purposes, such as where we store a password, or where you are able to customize the information you see. Recording cookies at such points is intended to make your online experience easier and faster. Commercial Bank’s cookies do not read your hard drive or contain any information that you have not already provided, and will not contain any information that will enable anyone to contact you via telephone or email. Most web browsers may be set to inform you when cookies are set or to prevent them from being recorded on your hard drive. The content of your email, your email address and Commercial Bank’s response, if any, is preserved so that we can better serve you. Depending on the content of your email, Commercial Bank may be required by existing laws and regulations to keep this information. If you send email to us, please remember that email is not secure against interception. If your email contains information that is sensitive, you may want to send this information via postal mail.
LOCATION OF PRODUCTS AND SERVICES Commercial Bank’s products and services are offered only in jurisdictions where they may be lawfully offered for sale and are subject to the terms of the applicable agreement. This Site is not intended for distribution to, or use by, any person or entity in any jurisdiction or county where such distribution or use would be contrary to local law or regulation. NOT ALL PRODUCTS OR SERVICES MENTIONED ON THIS WORLD WIDE WEB INTERNET SITE ARE AVAILABLE IN ALL JURISDICTIONS.
ADDITIONAL TERMS Certain sections or pages on this Site may contain separate terms and conditions, which are in addition to these terms and conditions. In the event of a conflict, the additional terms and conditions will govern those sections or pages.
COPYRIGHT COPYRIGHT COMMERCIAL BANK ©2001. ALL RIGHTS RESERVED. Copyright in the pages, in the screens displaying the pages, in the information and material therein and in their arrangement is owned by Commercial Bank, unless otherwise indicated.
Personal Checking
Manage Money Easily
Learn More
Mortgage Loans
Get Started Today
Apply Now
Questions?
